<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ozan İncesulu</title><link>https://ozyinc.com/</link><description>Recent content on Ozan İncesulu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ozyinc.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Implementing social share buttons</title><link>https://ozyinc.com/blog/socialsharing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ozyinc.com/blog/socialsharing/</guid><description>Background I was creating social share buttons for Facebook, Twitter, and Whatsapp some time ago. However, these social share buttons weren&amp;rsquo;t only for directly sharing a page&amp;rsquo;s link, but they should also render a custom dynamic title, description, and image based on what the user has entered into the website beforehand. I started reading the documentation of Facebook, Twitter and Whatsapp.
During the implementation phase, I have experienced some details, bits, and quirks of different sharing methods that I would like to share.</description></item><item><title>Ozan İncesulu's Curriculum Vitae</title><link>https://ozyinc.com/cv-detailed/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ozyinc.com/cv-detailed/</guid><description>Technical Skills Usage of POSIX environments (MacOS || Linux) on a daily basis. Knowledge and experience with Unit Testing, Integration Testing and TDD Worked with Docker &amp;amp; Kubernetes to build CI/CD pipelines. Knowledge of SQL databases; worked with SQLite, Google BigQuery, PostgreSQL. Knowledge of NoSQL, worked with MongoDB and ElasticSearch. Web development using Symfony, Django and Node.js libraries. Machine learning with SVM, RF and NN using scikit-learn and Keras.</description></item><item><title>Ozan İncesulu's Curriculum Vitae</title><link>https://ozyinc.com/cv/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ozyinc.com/cv/</guid><description>Technical Skills Usage of POSIX environments (MacOS || Linux) on a daily basis. Knowledge and experience with Unit Testing, Integration Testing and TDD Worked with Docker &amp;amp; Kubernetes to build CI/CD pipelines. Knowledge of SQL databases; worked with SQLite, Google BigQuery, PostgreSQL. Knowledge of NoSQL, worked with MongoDB and ElasticSearch. Web development using Symfony, Django and Node.js libraries. Machine learning with SVM, RF and NN using scikit-learn and Keras.</description></item><item><title>Creating my website in Github Pages using Hugo</title><link>https://ozyinc.com/blog/thispage/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ozyinc.com/blog/thispage/</guid><description>Background I have purchased the domain ozyinc.com a long time ago to host custom servers (work-related, hobby and Minecraft 😄 ), VPN server, etc&amp;hellip; however I have never started building my own website and for many years the homepage was an Express server behind an NGINX reverse proxy displaying Hello World on GET /.
The case with Elm and not-ever-finishing website Then, one day I wanted to try using Elm to build my customized page, being accustomed to the ecosystem for some time.</description></item><item><title>About Me!</title><link>https://ozyinc.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ozyinc.com/about/</guid><description>Hello World</description></item></channel></rss>